Um…
那…那個
Sis Sayo?
小夜姐？
The reason why I came here today is because I plan to settle down here.
我今天之所以過來 是因為我打算在這裡住下
From now on, please take care of me.
往後請多關照
Why do you want to stay here?
妳為什麼要住這裡？
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
《屍體如山的死亡遊戲》
I'll explain the reason later.
(第8集 The Assassin -暗殺者-) 我稍後再解釋理由
Do you need me to introduce myself first?
我需要先做個自我介紹嗎？
Yeah.
我可能需要
I can't possibly tell her that I knew who she is all along.
總不能告訴她我早就知道她是誰了吧
I'm Sayo Shinoyama.
我是四乃山小夜
I am Polka's niece, but I'm older than him.
我是波爾卡的姪女 但我的年紀比他大
This person is my sidekick,
這位則是我的“跟班”
supposedly a trainee butler named Lei.
據說是個見習管家 名叫雷
What do you mean by supposedly?
妳為什麼要用“據說”？
Because I have just found out today.
因為我也是今天才知道的
I'm Xiaoyu Lei.
我…我是雷小幽
Nice to meet you.
請多關照
I am Takumi Kuruya.
我是繰屋匠
I am Polka's business partner.
算是波爾卡的工作夥伴吧
And this person over here…
而這邊這位…
You must be Misaki. Long time no see.
妳是美咲吧 半天不見
We met again.
我們又見面了呢
So, Sis Sayo, why did you come here?
所以 小夜姐 妳為什麼會來這？
Sharks.
鯊魚
Sharks?
鯊魚？
The sharks were all burned.
我的鯊魚都被燒掉了
Right, they've all been burned.
沒錯 都被燒掉了
It's like what happened in the kitchen of Marine Medical Research Institute.
就像是海上醫學研究所的廚房裡 上演的那一幕一樣
That chef is amazing.
那個廚師真的很棒呢
Lady Sayo's room was
小夜大小姐的房間
destroyed by fire today.
在今天的火災中沒能倖免於難
Many of her shark-related items
她收藏的很多鯊魚週邊
were burned.
都被燒掉了
In addition, Lord Rozan asked me to bring a message to you.
此外 呂算大人也託我轉達一個消息
Oops, sorry about that.
嗨 不好意思啊
I wanted to have a good chat with you on the phone,
我本想在電話裡和你們好好聊聊的
Unfortunately, police and firefighters will ask me about the situation later.
可無奈的是 稍後消防和警方的人要找我詢問情況
Polka's and Sayo's rooms were both burned down.
波爾卡和小夜的房間正好都被燒掉了
So I apologize.
所以 抱歉啊
Let Sayo and the young man who serves as her guard
就讓小夜和擔任她護衛的小子
stay with you for a while.
在你那邊住一段時間吧
However, this is just a superficial reason.
不過 這不過是明面上的理由
If two people from my family were to live in that building,
若是我家有兩個人 在那棟大樓裡住下
it would be more convenient in various aspects.
就各種層面來說都比較方便
I can feel the increased surveillance
我能感覺到這棟大樓的四周
around this building,
監視這裡的氣息有所增加
and there's also him.
還有這孩子…
That's all.
我要轉達的就是這些
The people of Shinoyama have already learned about here,
四乃山家的人 已經得知了我在此處的落腳點
so Rozan sent out his own people
所以呂算才會派出自己的眼線
as personal bodyguard to come here.
作為隨身護衛來到這裡吧
However,
只不過
there is also a possibility that Sis Sayo may be a suspect attempting to kill Polka.
小夜姐也有可能 是試圖殺掉波爾卡的犯人
Sand Sharks and Avalanche Sharks,
《瘋狂食人鯊》和《暴雪飛鯊》 這兩部電影
which one do you prefer?
妳比較喜歡哪一部？
I like both!
兩部我都喜歡
If it really is her, it would save me a lot of effort.
如果真的是她 我倒是能省下不少功夫
Good morning. What a wonderful morning.
早安 真是不錯的早晨呢
Morning.
呃 早安
This kind of morning can make people feel energetic.
這樣的早晨可以讓人充滿活力
Don't you think so?
你不這麼認為嗎？
Hmm, I do feel that way indeed.
嗯 的確有這種感覺呢
Well, I don't think so.
我可不這樣想
But I will respect your opinion.
但我會尊重你的意見
Good night.
晚安
What is she talking about?
這傢伙剛起床就在說什麼呢
Good morning.
早啊
I am sorry.
十分抱歉
The young lady has not yet recovered. She is still frightened.
大小姐還沒能從 受驚的狀態中恢復過來
She may just want to lie down
一時半會
and sleep for the moment.
她可能只想躺著睡覺
If you want me to crawl out of my sleeping bag,
如果想讓我從睡袋裡爬出來
I recommend trying shark bait.
推薦你們用鯊魚週邊來釣釣看
Yeah, you wish.
妳這傢伙想得倒是挺美
We need to find an empty room,
我們得去找個空房間
tidy it up, and let them stay there.
收拾一下 然後給他們住才行
Let's go buy a set of mattresses in Don Quijote.
我們去唐吉軻德買套床墊吧
You can't keep sleeping on the floor all the time.
你們總不能一直打地舖吧
As long as I have a shark sleeping bag,
我只要有鯊魚睡袋
I can sleep anywhere. So there's no need to worry about it.
就可以在任何地方睡覺 所以你們就不必費心了
I can fall asleep even while standing up,
我站著也能睡著
so it's not a problem.
所以沒關係的
How could that not be a problem?
怎麼可能沒關係啊
No problem. Don't worry.
沒關係的 各位不必擔心
Taking care of the young lady's
照顧大小姐的日常起居
daily life is my responsibility.
是我的職責
Speaking of which,
說起來
why were you sent to take care of Sis Sayo?
為什麼你會被派來照顧小夜姐？
I was chosen because my name is similar to lady Sayo's.
我是因為和小夜大小姐的名字相似 所以才被選上的
What a hasty reason.
真是草率的理由啊
Besides serving as the bodyguard of the young lady,
除了擔任大小姐的護衛以外
I also have to act as a liaison for young master Polka.
我還要在一些瑣事上 充當波爾卡少爺的聯絡人
I see.
這樣啊
What is the current situation at home?
家裡現在是什麼情況
There's no need to use honorifics with me, young master Polka.
您沒必要對我用敬語 波爾卡少爺
In the courtyard of the Shinoyama,
四乃山家的大院裡
it seems that a group of police officers have come today.
今天好像也來了一堆警察
Therefore, it is better for us not to go back temporarily.
所以我們暫時還是不要回去比較好
I see. I see.
原來如此 原來如此
When you came to your senses, the arsonist was controlled and transferred to police.
待你們回過神來時縱火犯已經被打倒 於是你們便將他交給了警察
Who are they?
喂 那些人是誰？
Police officers.
好像是警察
No way.
不會吧
Oh.
哎呀
I thought the police interrogation had already ended yesterday.
我還以為警察的偵訊 昨天就已經結束了
Nice to meet you.
幸會幸會
Our department is somewhat different from others.
我們隸屬的部門有些不太一樣
Please cooperate with our investigation.
麻煩您配合一下我們的調查
Mr. Takeru Shinoyama.
四乃山尊先生
So, the true identity of the arsonist from yesterday
這麼說 昨天那名縱火犯的真實身份
is perhaps the Firestarter.
也許是“赴火之蟲”囉
Yes, it might be.
沒錯 是有這樣的可能性
But I really can't immediately believe such claims.
不過我實在沒法立刻就相信這種說法
If it is true as you say,
若真如你們所言
and I heard that the culprit has already died,
我聽說犯人昨天已經死了
can I assume there will be no more fires caused by the Firestarter?
所以我可以理解為往後“赴火之蟲” 不會再出來引發火災了嗎
I never said that.
不不 我可沒有這麼說
It's just that
只不過
in order to reveal the truth,
為了讓真相水落石出
we must investigate this matter thoroughly.
我們必須將這件事調查得一清二楚
The Firestarter was originally the enemy of Shinoyama Security.
“赴火之蟲”原本就是 我們四乃山警備的天敵
He burned down several buildings that we were responsible for,
由我們負責安保的大樓 也有幾棟被他給燒掉了
and we really can't afford to lose face.
我們面子上實在是掛不住
We don't know when the police will be able to catch him and bring him to justice,
不知道警察什麼時候 才能將他抓捕歸案
so we are very worried.
我們可是擔心得很啊
This is harsh.
這話聽起來真是刺耳
Furthermore,
更何況
even if you catch him,
就算已經抓起來了 可要是之後讓他越獄了
it will be meaningless if he escapes later.
那也沒什麼意義
What a dagger in the heart.
真是句句在戳我們的痛處
Aren't you two from Shinjuku Police Station?
兩位是新宿警察局的人吧
Is it alright to waste time here?
來這種地方浪費時間真的好嗎？
Tena Sorimura, nicknamed Phantom Solitaire.
雪車村天鵶 綽號“怪人雪天鴉”
-He was active in Shinjuku. -Catch me if you can.
-那傢伙應該是以新宿為據點活動的 -有本事就來抓我啊
The prime minister's kidnapping incident in the past
過去他犯下的首相綁架事件
has implicated even unrelated people like us, resulting in a drop in stock prices.
曾讓我們這些毫無關聯的人 也受到了牽連 導致股價跟著下跌
We hope that the police
還希望警方
can prevent our stock prices from continuing to fall.
能夠不讓我們的股價繼續下跌
I look forward to
我很期待
all of your positive performances.
諸位的積極表現
The two people following him
跟在他身後的那兩個人
are probably acting as assassins.
多半也在做殺手的工作
Really?
真的假的
I can feel it just from the atmosphere,
我靠氛圍就感覺得出來
especially from that man. I smell a similar scent on him.
尤其是那個男的 我在他的身上嗅到了同類的味道
A similar scent?
同類？
He's likely a violent person.
他大概是屬於那種 認為什麼事都能靠暴力解決的人
In other words,
換句話說
he's a jerk.
他就是個混蛋
That sounds quite scary.
那還蠻可怕的嘛
Go tell Tozawa and Yatsu that
你去和戶澤大叔 還有八津打聲招呼吧
depending on the situation,
視情況
we might have conflicts with Shinoyama.
我們也許會和四乃山起衝突
Have you had any clues?
你是掌握到什麼線索了嗎？
That's a photo displayed in their home.
這是擺在他們家裡的照片
You should remember
最左邊的那個人
the person on the far left, right?
你應該有印象吧
He is…
這傢伙是…
He's Polka Shinoyama.
他叫四乃山波爾卡
Rozan's second son,
是呂算當家的次子
which means he's the young master of Shinoyama.
也就是說 他是四乃山家的少爺
However, it seems that he is not at home now.
雖然他現在好像不在家
He appeared at the scene of the fire yesterday.
但他昨天曾出現在那起火災的現場
So he's one of the Shinoyama?
那小鬼 原來是四乃山家的人啊
And the girl with glasses who was with him
而和他待在一起的 那個戴眼鏡的小姑娘
left her footprints at the scene of Human Knot.
“人體打結”的現場 則是留有她的腳印
It is said that there was a dispute between the group of people
被打結在一起的那幫人
who are tied together and an organization under the Shinoyama Group.
據說他們跟四乃山集團旗下的組織 存在糾紛
In the past month, calamities have been occurring frequently.
近來這一個月 災厄接連不斷地冒出來
Is Polka or Takeru Shinoyama
位於這一連串事件的中心的人 究竟是波爾卡
at the center of this series of events?
還是四乃山尊呢
Let us discover the truth behind it.
就由我們來揭露背後的真相吧
Yeah.
是吧？
Tsubaki Iwanome?
岩野目椿嗎
He used to have an affair with the inspector,
他之前曾和監察官勾搭在一起
Neither bribery nor pressure worked on him.
賄賂和施壓在他身上都不管用
Do you want me to kill him?
要幹掉他嗎？
There's no need to bother. Just let it be.
用不著 就隨他去吧
I hope he can unravel
希望他能夠解開波爾卡身上的謎團
Speaking of which,
而且
it seems that Grandpa
我爺爺他那邊
is up to something.
好像也有什麼動作呢
Sis Sayo, you can use this room.
小夜姐 你們就用這個房間吧
Sorry that we need you to help move things.
抱歉 還要麻煩你們幫忙搬東西
It's okay.
沒關係沒關係
By the way, are you really going to sleep in such a small room?
話說 你真的要睡在 這麼小的房間裡嗎？
Yes, no problem at all.
是的 沒有問題
Thank you very much for helping us.
十分感謝諸位伸出援手
Good night.
晚安
There are more people living here now.
住在這的人變多了
It feels like it's getting more interesting.
感覺越來越有趣了呢
Yeah.
是啊
But speaking of which, Polka,
不過話說回來 波爾卡
how do you plan to arrange those two people?
那兩個人你打算怎麼辦
Well, after all, the divination house is reopening tomorrow.
嗯 畢竟占卜屋明天就要重新營業了
How should I explain it to them?
我該怎麼向他們解釋才好
Although I'm not sure why Master trusts him,
雖然我不清楚主公大人為什麼相信他
nevertheless, let me reveal his true identity.
不過就由我來揭穿他的真面目吧
This imposter Polka Shinoyama.
這個假冒的四乃山波爾卡
What do you mean, Master?
您這是什麼意思 主公大人
Just like what you heard,
就和你聽到的一樣
can you accompany Sayo to go to Shinjuku?
你可以陪著小夜去一趟新宿嗎
I got it, Master.
我明白了 主公大人
I just have to kill the fake Polka, right?
我只要解決掉那個假波爾卡就行了吧
Exactly the opposite, you fool.
剛好相反 蠢貨
You are already a guard of the Shinoyama.
你已經是四乃山家的護衛了
There's no need for you to do the dirty work.
髒活就不用由你來做了
That polka is indeed fake,
那個波爾卡的確是假的
but he is not an enemy.
但他不是敵人
Why?
這是怎麼回事
Is the real Polka alive?
真正的波爾卡還活著嗎？
How should I put it? He's still relatively safe.
啊…怎麼說呢 他還算是平安吧
Anyway, I can't explain it clearly to you.
總之 我跟你解釋不清楚
But I am sure about that guy's identity.
不過我可以為那傢伙的身份做保證
You need to protect Sayo and the fake Polka.
你去保護小夜和假的波爾卡
Can you do it, Xiaoyu?
你應該做得到吧 小幽
Well, there's nothing I can do.
那就沒辦法了
After all, I cannot go against your order.
畢竟我不能違背主公大人的命令
If you don't want to, it's fine.
無妨 你要是不願意的話就算了
It's okay, I'll just do it.
不不 我做就是了
I will protect them. You can rest assured, Master.
我會保護他們的 你就放心休息吧 主公大人
This is an opportunity.
這是個機會
Let me get rid
就由我來除掉
of the poisonous insects that get close to Master,
接近主公大人的毒蟲吧
and
然後
if the real Polka is still alive,
若是真正的波爾卡還活著
I will get rid of him as well.
我就順便將他一併除掉
Moreover,
而且說到底
a fragile guy like him
他那種柔弱的傢伙
is actually the Master's son. I cannot accept this at all.
居然是主公大人的兒子什麼的 這我完全無法接受
I am far more
我遠比波爾卡
useful than Polka
要有用處得多
and better suited to be Lord Rozan's son.
我比他更適合當呂算大人的兒子
I am not broken yet.
我還…沒有…壞掉
He can't be saved anymore.
他已經沒救了
Unexpectedly, he encountered Agakura on his first job.
沒想到他第一次工作就碰上了阿牙倉
He only lost his limbs,
僅僅丟掉了四肢
which is fortunate in misfortune.
這已是他不幸中的萬幸
From now on, let's use Xiaoyu as the t'ing-fu.
往後就將小幽作為庭壺吧
No way.
不是吧
No, Father.
不要 父親
I still have value. I am still alive.
我還有用處 我還活著
Don't do it. This isn't real. Save me.
不要 這不是真的 救救我
Why, Father?
為什麼 父親
No. Stop it. Save me. Kill you!
不要 住手 救救我 幹掉你
If you dare to do anything to me, I will kill you.
要是敢對我做什麼 我就殺掉你
Go die, go die.
去死去死去死去死去死
Hey, what's t'ing-fu?
喂 庭壺是什麼
Lord Rozan.
呂算大人
I'm afraid you can't bear to hear that.
我的話怕是會髒了您的耳朵
In its literal meaning, the so-called t'ing-fu
如字面意思 所謂的“庭壺”
is the vessel that has been passed down in our family.
就是我們一族代代相傳的“器”
The toxins contained in the poisons we use
我們使用的毒藥中所含的毒素
can only be cultivated using
有些只能用活生生的孩童的內臟
the organs of living children.
才能夠培養出來
Don't say it so terrifyingly.
你不要說得那麼恐怖嘛
Are you planning to use your own son for that kind of thing?
你是打算用自己的兒子做那種事嗎
Forgive me for being presumptuous, but people of our family,
恕我冒昧 我們一族的人
whether parents or children,
不論是雙親還是兒女
are not considered "humans" but rather "objects."
都不是“人”而是“物品”
Showing compassion towards broken objects
對壞掉的道具抱有惻隱之心
is equivalent to disrespecting our family and our work.
就等同於在蔑視我們一族和工作
This matter is closely related to your safety.
這件事跟保護您的安危也密切相關
Please do not interfere.
請你不要干涉
Oh, I see.
這樣啊
If you just treat him as an "object",
如果你只是把他當作“物品”來看待
then it shouldn't be a problem for me to buy him.
那我把他買下來應該不成問題吧
What?
什麼？
Don't use "He's an important family member" as an excuse to refuse to sell to me.
事到如今 你可別拿“他是重要的家人 所以不賣”來當藉口拒絕我喔
As the "hand" of our family, he does not have any value.
他作為我們一族的“手” 雖不具有任何價值
But he still has value as a t'ing-fu.
可他仍然具有作為“庭壺”的價值
We will not sell him cheaply to you.
我們是不會便宜賣給您的
Well, this isn't a bad thing for you either.
嗯 這對你們來說也不是壞事
I'll prioritize the offer of the latest technology of Shinoyama Group,
我會優先給你們提供 四乃山集團的最新技術
so you can keep working in this field,
即便不用製作那種無聊的毒藥
even if it doesn't involve making those poisons.
你們也能繼續在這行幹下去
What were they discussing just now?
從剛才開始 他們到底在商量些什麼啊
Don't treat me as a good person.
你不要把我當成好人
I just want to get test subjects
我只是想得到實驗體罷了
for testing the latest prosthesis.
為了用來測試最新型的義肢
Another thing is,
還有就是
if you could move, it would be great.
如果你能動起來就好了
Just keep me company and chat with me about my family.
你就陪著我聊一聊我的家人吧
When was the last time
上一次有人對我露出笑容
someone smiled at me?
是多久以前的事了呢
Master.
主公大人
The Shinoyama is not just a wealthy family.
四乃山家不是單純的富豪
They have connections
他們與黑白兩道上的
with both the underworld and legitimate organizations.
很多組織都存在聯繫
I heard that there is also a killer organization like mine.
我聽說那裡面也有 跟我們這一樣的殺手組織
So you're saying the person who entrusted us to kill Polka
這麼說 委託我們殺掉波爾卡的人
is probably not from the Shinoyama family, right?
其實應該不是四乃山家的人嗎
Instead of hiring assassins from here,
與其僱傭我們這裡的殺手
they might as well let their own men shoot him dead.
還不如讓自己的手下一槍蹦掉他
It's hard to say.
這可不好說
If I were in the same position as the client,
如果我和委託人站在相同的立場上
I would probably also seek help from external parties.
我大概也會藉助外部人士的力量
It would be manageable if Polka Shinoyama was hated by the whole family.
若是四乃山波爾卡 遭到全族厭惡的話那還好說
But he is the son favored
可他是深受當家
by the head of the family, Rozan Shinoyama
四乃山呂算寵愛的兒子
If they assign their own man to kill him
殺掉他這種工作
and that person betrays them, they will lose everything.
交給親信來辦的話 若是遭到背叛就滿盤皆輸了
As for the actual situation,
就實際情況而言
what kind of people are on the assassin team
四乃山家雇傭的殺手組織裡
employed by Shinoyama?
都有什麼樣的人呢？
Let me think.
我想想
The most frequently mentioned one is the Lei family,
最常聽人提到的
which has bases in Shanghai, Hong Kong and Yokohama.
是在上海 香港以及橫濱 都設有據點的雷家
Although it doesn't have a rare title,
雖說不是什麼稀奇的名號
the situation of the Lei family related to Shinoyama is quite special.
不過跟四乃山 存在聯繫的雷家情況比較特別
They are known as Heilei.
他們被稱為“黑雷”
They are a family that has combined old and new technologies,
是融合了新舊技術的一族
including ancient poisons passed down through generations
其中包括從遠古流傳下來的毒藥
and the latest technology provided by Shinoyama.
以及四乃山家提供的最新技術
Their range of expertise is extremely wide.
涉獵範圍極其廣泛
Anyway, let's just do it as usual.
總之 我們照往常那樣來就行了吧
Yes.
也是
Sis Sayo should know that I am engaged in divination.
小夜姐應該也知道我在做占卜的工作
That thing you mentioned yesterday,
你昨天提到的那個
if I remember correctly, it is called the poison dragon, right?
我記得是“廢毒龍”吧？
Are there any other types of dragons?
還有什麼其他的龍嗎？
Lewd and Cruel Dragon Marufi,
化身為人類的帥哥美女誆騙王族的
who impersonated attractive men and women to deceive the royal family.
“淫虐龍瑪爾芬”
Although it is a formidable troublemaker,
雖然牠是個令人生畏的麻煩傢伙
it fell in love with a general from Imperial Gorgeous Unit.
不過牠愛上了帝國絢爛隊的將軍
During the disintegration of the Empire, it ran away with the general.
在帝國分崩離析之際 牠帶著將軍跑掉了
It's so romantic
和龍談戀愛
to fall in love with a dragon.
好浪漫啊
And there are Steam Dragon Goronson and Bladedragon Murm.
還有就是“蒸氣龍戈隆松” 以及“圓刃龍姆魯姆”
The material of the dragon has a high value in trading.
龍的素材在交易時具有很高的價值
If you want to make a zombie dragon, you must buy the whole piece.
如果要製作殭屍龍 就必須得買下一整條龍才行
These two guys have only been talking
這兩個傢伙從剛才開始就只有在聊
about games, comics,
遊戲和漫畫的事情
or light novel since just now.
還是說是輕小說裡的內容？
What's going on? Are they high school students?
什麼情況啊 他們是中學生嗎
And what is that clanging sound?
還有這匡噹匡噹的聲音究竟是什麼
It feels like piles of bones dancing.
感覺像是成堆的骸骨在跳舞
Isn't this just a waste of magic?
你這不是在白白浪費魔力嗎
It's fine.
這種程度的話沒什麼大不了的
Are they playing games?
他們是在玩遊戲嗎
It doesn't sound like it though.
可是聽起來不太像啊
IT WOULD BE GREAT IF THE REMAINING AND CONSUMED AMOUNT It seems like he's writing something.
(嗯…要是能像遊戲裡一樣把魔法的餘量) 他們好像在寫什麼東西
OF MAGIC IN NUMBERS THROUGH DATA COULD BE DISPLAYED, JUST LIKE IN GAMES.
(和消耗量數値化 通過數據顯示出來就好了)
Could it be that they are playing TRPG?
他們該不會在玩桌遊吧？
This is the sound of dice rolling.
這是骰子發出的聲音
Speaking of which,
話說回來
that guy's name is Xiaoyu, right?
那個人是叫小幽吧？
He is very dedicated to his work.
他對工作很是上心呢
Even at this time, he hasn't slept yet. It seems like he's protecting Sis Sayo.
都這個時間了 他還沒睡 好像是在保護小夜姐
He hasn't slept?
他還沒睡？
He is standing in front of Sis Sayo's room.
嗯 他就站在小夜姐的房間前面
This guy has sensed my presence again.
這傢伙又察覺到我的氣息了
There are no surveillance cameras or anything like that here.
這裡明明沒有監控攝像頭那種東西
I'm going back.
我該回去了
I see.
原來如此
He wanted to remind me that he is well aware of the situation here.
他是想提醒我 他對我這邊的動向一清二楚嗎
It's fine.
也好
Let me bet with the blood of Heilei.
就讓我賭上“黑雷”之血
Even if I have to stake Lord Rozan's reputation,
不 就算賭上呂算大人的名號
I will gradually reveal your true identity.
我也要一點一點地揭露你的真面目
SHINJUKU POLICE STATION
(新宿警察局)
Listen carefully. You all need to remember clearly.
聽好了 你們都給我記清楚了
This person is Polka Shinoyama, aged 16.
這個人是四乃山波爾卡 16歲
The one who acted with him is the girl A,
跟他一起行動的 就是在“人體打結”事件中
who left footprints at the scene of the Human Knot incident.
在現場留下腳印的少女A
Who painted that picture?
那幅畫是誰畫的
It's me.
是我畫的
His mother, Kanon Shinoyama, passed away.
他的母親四乃山卡農已經過世
Although I would like to say that
他就是大戶人家的小少爺
he is the young master of a wealthy family,
雖然我很想這麼說
it seems that the actual situation is much more complicated.
但貌似實際情況要複雜得多
Polka Shinoyama has now left his home.
四乃山波爾卡現在離開了自己的家
Besides going in and out of Clarissa's bar,
除了出入克拉麗莎的酒吧以外
according to himself,
根據他本人的證言
In addition, he told Arase something strange.
另外 他還對荒瀨說了一件奇怪的事
My parents sold me, so I'm not very knowledgeable about this sort of thing.
我是被父母賣掉的 所以不是很清楚這種事
THEY WENT TOGETHER TO THE SHINOYAMA HOUSE? GIRL A
(一同前往四乃山家？少女A)
Currently, we are not sure about the meaning of his words.
目前我們還不清楚 他那句話是什麼意思
It is also difficult to determine whether there is a connection with this incident.
也難以斷定 那句話和這次的事件是否存在聯繫
However,
不過呢
the words that people speak,
人們口中吐露的話語
regardless of their truthfulness, have their own meanings.
不論真假都有其意義
As long as we explore the true meaning and make him doubt himself,
我們只要通過探尋其中的真意 令對方產生動搖
we can see through his true intentions.
就能看穿他的真面目
I investigated the whereabouts of Polka.
然後 我調查了一下 這名叫做波爾卡的少年的動向
To my surprise,
沒有想到
he has become a diviner in Shinjuku.
他居然在新宿的中心地帶 當起了占卜師
I bet Solitaire is thrilled. How annoying.
雪天鴉那混蛋想必高興壞了吧 可惡
What?
什麼
GAME OVER
(遊戲結束)
Have a nice day.
十分感謝您的光顧
I didn't expect that in such a short time when I was in prison,
沒想到在我蹲監獄這麼短的時間裡
VR technology would evolve to this level.
VR技術竟然進化到了這種地步
It's truly amazing.
著實精彩
Civilized progress can also
文明的進步
bring innovation to the world of magic.
亦能為魔術的世界帶來革新
Huh? Is that Tena Sorimura?
咦 那個人是雪車村天鵶吧？
So now it's time
那麼接下來
to start thinking about what to perform after six days.
我是時候該考慮考慮 六天後要表演什麼了
As for what actions the police will take in this week,
至於警察會在這一週內採取何種行動
I'm really looking forward to checking them out.
我還真是期待啊
Hey! Stop there!
給我站住 喂
What I'm looking forward to is not this kind of solo action.
我期待的可不是這種單獨行動啊
Bye, Akechi.
再會了 明智
The second me and the third me are finally going to appear.
終於到第二個 第三個的我 現身的時候了嗎
FORTUNE TELLING I haven't dressed up like this for a while.
(開運 占卜) 我有段時間沒有打扮成這樣了
We suddenly decided to reopen.
我們突然決定重新開始營業
Will there be any customers?
會有客人來嗎
After all, we have been closed for many days.
畢竟我們歇業了好多天嘛
Oh, sorry. We will work in the afternoon.
啊 抱歉 我們今天是從下午開始營業
Hey.
嗨
The last time we met was at Clarissa's bar.
我們上次見面 還是在克拉麗莎的酒吧呢
Polka Shinoyama.
四乃山波爾卡
Hi.
你…你好
Can you help me with divination?
你可以替我占卜一下嗎？
(Episode 9: The Signpost)
(#09 The Signpost -路標-)